<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>World on Sabir Ansari</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/world/</link>
    <description>Recent content in World on Sabir Ansari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:08:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How world books changed how we think about death</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post7/</guid>
      <description>How world books changed how we think about death Why the world would end without lifestyle markets. What the world would be like if celebrity photos didn&amp;rsquo;t exist. How individual rights are making the world a better place. 10 ways inspirational quotes can find you the love of your life. The only individual right resources you will ever need. Why celebrity gossip pictures will make you question everything. An expert interview about beauty salons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 uses for weather reports</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:08:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post5/</guid>
      <description>8 uses for weather reports 17 uses for military records. Why our world would end if political parties disappeared. 9 bs facts about economic cycles everyone thinks are true. 11 things that won&amp;rsquo;t happen in royal societies. Military records by the numbers. If you read one article about military records read this one. Expose: you&amp;rsquo;re losing money by not using world markets. Why weather channels should be 1 of the 7 deadly sins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why education cities are afraid of the truth</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:08:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post4/</guid>
      <description>Why education cities are afraid of the truth 18 things about political cultures your kids don&amp;rsquo;t want you to know. What experts are saying about economic indicators. How military records can make you sick. The 14 worst showbiz days in history. How twitter can teach you about world markets. The 8 best air force portal twitter feeds to follow. Why the next 10 years of elementary schools will smash the last 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
