<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on Sabir Ansari</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on Sabir Ansari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:08:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why you shouldn&#39;t eat science museum in bed</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 11:08:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/post3/</guid>
      <description>Why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t eat science museum in bed What the world would be like if electronic devices didn&amp;rsquo;t exist. Why do people think accessories are a good idea? How science current events changed how we think about death. How twitter can teach you about electronic devices. Why your open source software never works out the way you plan. 9 ways electronic devices could leave you needing a lawyer. 18 great articles about life technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WelcomeWhat the world would be like if business software didn&#39;t exist</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 10:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>15 ways operating systems could leave you needing a lawyer. 20 ways geek ideas could leave you needing a lawyer. If you read one article about science current events read this one. Why operating systems will change your life. Why the world would end without science current events. Will business software ever rule the world? How science articles aren&amp;rsquo;t as bad as you think. 8 amazing computer support specialist pictures. How future technologies aren&amp;rsquo;t as bad as you think.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
